sms2friends.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy - - sms2friends

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for all pages and  
services offered by sms2friends.com

### Personally Provided Information

You do not have to give us personal information to visit sms2friends.com. If  
you choose to provide us with additional information through an e-mail message,  
inquiry form, comments, etc., we maintain the information as long as needed to  
respond to your question, inquiry, or to fulfill the stated purpose of the  
communication as well as archive them for some statistical reasons. Except for  
authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not give, share, sell or  
transfer any personal information to a third party.

### Website Traffic Analysis Software

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available  
to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify  
unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause  
damage. We also monitor our traffic to analyze visitorss information, such as,  
but not limited to, operating system, browsers, screen resolutions and similar.

In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to  
any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help  
identify an individual.

### Group Subscription

If users wish to subscribe to our group, we ask for contact information. Our  
“SMS of the day” feature is powered by Google Groups. Recipients of our  
newsletters can unsubscribe using the instructions listed at the end of the  
e-mail.

### SMS Subscription / Alerts

You are asked to provide certain information if you request to receive daily  
SMS alerts. We collect this information to keep our SMS broadcast as per the  
dynamics of our subscribers. Like all other instances, this information will  
never be given/sold to third party, otherwise asked by the the Law of the Land.

### Third Party Advertising Partners

### Cookies And Web Beacons

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  
Google use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
We also use third party advertisements on our site to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

### Valueclickmedia

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this ?behavioral advertising? practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml

### External Links

Our web sites contain links to other sites. sms2friends.com is not  
responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We  
encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy  
statements of each web site to which we may link that may collect personal  
information.

### Responsibily

sms2friends.com’s team cannot be held responsible for any activity resulting  
any kind of loss to an individual or group.

Note: This Page can get updated any time, without an prior notice, so keep  
checking back.

Last updated: June 13th, 2013
